const foodWordsEnRu = {
  set_id: "djfhskd3849837563jhfdbovajkvd",
  set_title: "Английские слова: Еда",
  date_of_create: "2024-01-27",
  lang: "ru",
  instructions: "Выберите перевод на русский язык.",
  category: "английский язык",
  set_cards: [
    {
      question: "Apple",
      answer: "Яблоко",
      options: ["Груша", "Яблоко", "Банан", "Виноград"],
    },
    {
      question: "Bread",
      answer: "Хлеб",
      options: ["Торт", "Печенье", "Хлеб", "Булка"],
    },
    {
      question: "Cheese",
      answer: "Сыр",
      options: ["Масло", "Сыр", "Йогурт", "Творог"],
    },
    {
      question: "Milk",
      answer: "Молоко",
      options: ["Сметана", "Кефир", "Молоко", "Сок"],
    },
    {
      question: "Egg",
      answer: "Яйцо",
      options: ["Яйцо", "Котлета", "Колбаса", "Сосиска"],
    },
    {
      question: "Chicken",
      answer: "Курица",
      options: ["Утка", "Говядина", "Курица", "Свинина"],
    },
    {
      question: "Fish",
      answer: "Рыба",
      options: ["Рыба", "Краб", "Креветка", "Мидия"],
    },
    {
      question: "Potato",
      answer: "Картофель",
      options: ["Огурец", "Томат", "Картофель", "Свекла"],
    },
    {
      question: "Carrot",
      answer: "Морковь",
      options: ["Морковь", "Редис", "Репа", "Капуста"],
    },
    {
      question: "Soup",
      answer: "Суп",
      options: ["Суп", "Борщ", "Солянка", "Уха"],
    },
    {
      question: "Salad",
      answer: "Салат",
      options: ["Салат", "Оливье", "Винегрет", "Цезарь"],
    },
    {
      question: "Rice",
      answer: "Рис",
      options: ["Гречка", "Макароны", "Рис", "Кускус"],
    },
    {
      question: "Pasta",
      answer: "Паста",
      options: ["Пельмени", "Паста", "Ризотто", "Пицца"],
    },
    {
      question: "Meat",
      answer: "Мясо",
      options: ["Рыба", "Мясо", "Курица", "Колбаса"],
    },
    {
      question: "Butter",
      answer: "Масло",
      options: ["Маргарин", "Масло", "Сметана", "Майонез"],
    },
  ],
}

export default foodWordsEnRu;
